{
    "subject": "resource/Blue_Seed",
    "predicate": "property/originalairdate",
    "object": "1994-12-21",
    "human_readable": "The original air date of Blue Seed was December 21, 1994.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8411142230033875,
            "question": "What month was the original air date of Blue Seed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7020716667175293,
            "question": "When did Blue Seed first air?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5663735270500183,
            "question": "In what year did Blue Seed premiere?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4552009105682373,
            "question": "Where was Blue Seed originally broadcast?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38316333293914795,
            "question": "Who created Blue Seed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2782260775566101,
            "question": "What is the plot of Blue Seed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21209949254989624,
            "question": "What is the genre of Blue Seed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18544700741767883,
            "question": "Is Blue Seed a television show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18029572069644928,
            "question": "Does Blue Seed have a sequel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11007101088762283,
            "question": "Is Blue Seed a popular anime series?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The original air date of Blue Seed was December 21, 1994.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3021_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Blue Seed have a sequel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3021_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Blue Seed a television show?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3021_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the genre of Blue Seed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3021_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3021_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3021_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3021_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3021_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3021_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3021_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3021_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3021_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3021_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3021_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that the original air date for Blue Seed was October 5, 1994.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe context information contains the following text:\n\n\"It originally aired in Japan from October 5, 1994, to March 29, 1995.\"\n\nThis indicates that the original air date of Blue Seed was not December 21, 1994, but rather from October 5, 1994, to March 29, 1995. Therefore, the answer is \"no\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Blue Seed originally aired in Japan from October 5, 1994, to March 29, 1995. There is no mention of December 21, 1994, as an air date for the show."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The original air date of Blue Seed was from October 5, 1994, to March 29, 1995, not December 21, 1994.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It contradicts information provided in context points 4 and 5, which state the original air date was October 5, 1994.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The original air date of Blue Seed was October 5, 1994, to March 29, 1995, as stated in context information.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context clearly states that Blue Seed originally aired from October 5, 1994, to March 29, 1995, which does not include December 21, 1994.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}